kcumb.edu 2015-03-16

# Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences

## Privacy Policy

By accessing or using Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences' website, you agree to the terms of Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences Online Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

### Collection of Personal Information

When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as enrollment and event registration, Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. If you elect to engage in these online activities, Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences may require that you provide us personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information. You may also be asked to provide a credit card number.

When you submit personal information to Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences, you understand and agree that Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences and its subsidiaries, affiliates and trusted vendors may transfer, store, and process your profile. Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences collects this information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of this information. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

Your personal information is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access to it. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.

### Use of Cookies

When you visit Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, recording your passwords and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. While Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences uses cookies to track your visit, our Web Site and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences with personal information.

Please note that Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any other website that Kansas City University of Medicine and Biosciences may link to.
